Guide to the David Hamburg papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Carnegie Corporation of New York
  - Subseries I.8: Eastern Block
    - Sub-subseries I.8.B: Background
      - Kennan Institute reports and background on Gorbachev speeches, 1985-1987 (Box 191, Folder 1-66)
      - Harriman Institute materials; Condoleeza Rice; etc., 1987-1989 (Box 192, Folder 1-60)
      - Harriman Institute materials; Condoleeza Rice; etc., 1989-1990 (Box 193, Folder 1-50)
      - Conference papers, 1990-1991 (Box 194, Folder 1-40)
      - Press Clippings re: Moscow Conference, 1991- (Box 195, Folder 1-30)
      - Former Soviet Union:3rd party papers & memoranda, 1991-1997 (Box 196, Folder 1-67)
      - Program on New Approaches to Russian Security; etc., 1997-2002 (Box 197, Folder 1-42)
    - Sub-subseries I.8.C: Velikhov-Hamburg
      Materials document the projects, including VelHam Computer Project and International Foundation for the Survival and Development of Humanity, undertaken in collaboration with Yevgeny P. Velikhov, a physicist, a vice president of the Soviet Academy of Sciences, and a frequent adviser to Secretary General Mikhail S. Gorbachev, who was considered one of the most influential scientists in the Soviet Union
      - Background Materials General, undated- (Box 197, Folder 43-69)
      - Materials, December 1985-1987 (Box 198, Folder 1-26)
      - Project files, 1988-March 1988 (Box 199, Folder 1-19)
        See also box 205
      - Project files, April 1988-1989 (Box 200, Folder 1-39)
      - Project files and email, 1990-1991 (Box 201, Folder 1-18)
      - Email, January 1992-February 1992 (Box 202, Folder 1-6)
      - Email & email directory, March 1992-April 1992 (Box 203, Folder 1-7)
      - Email, May 1992-July 1992 (Box 204, Folder 1-6)
      - Project files, undated- (Box 204, Folder 7-9)
      - Project files, 1985-1988 (Box 205, Folder 1-23)
  - Subseries I.9: General and Administrative
    Internal memoranda, reports, notes, correspondence and other materials related to general administration of Carnegie Corporation of New York, grants, mixed program area materials, staffing and personnel issues etc. The subseries also contains correspondence relating to Hamburg assuming the presidency of Carnegie Corporation and his retirement from presidency.
    - Cumulative lists, new program areas, 1979-1995 (Box 616)
    - Carnegie Presidency, 1982-1983 (Box 617)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1983-1988 (Box 618)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1984-1985 (Box 619)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1984-1985 (Box 620)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1984-1991 (Box 621)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1985- (Box 622)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1985-1986 (Box 623)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1985-1987 (Box 624)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1985-1988 (Box 625)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1986-1987 (Box 626)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1986-1988 (Box 627)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1986-1997 (Box 814)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1987-1988 (Box 628)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1987-1988 (Box 629)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1987-1988 (Box 630)
    - Administrative and Latin America files, 1987-1988 (Box 631)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1988- (Box 632)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1988- (Box 633)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1988-1990 (Box 634)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1988-1992 (Box 635)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1988-1995 (Box 636)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1989-1994 (Box 637)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1989-1996 (Box 638)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1990-1991 (Box 639)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1991-1992 (Box 640)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1991-1993 (Box 641)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1992- (Box 642)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1992-1994 (Box 643)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1994-1995 (Box 644)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1995-1996 (Box 645)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1995-1996 (Box 646)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1997-1998 (Box 647)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1998-1999 (Box 648)
    - Administrative and subject files, 1997-1998 (Box 649)
  - Subseries I.10: Committee on International Security and Arms Control (CISAC)
    The National Academy of Sciences (NAS) formed the Committee on International Security and Arms Control (CISAC) in 1980 as a permanent committee to bring the resources of the Academy to bear on critical problems of international security and arms control. CISAC’s security dialogues with Russia (since 1981) and China (since 1988) addressed technical and potentially sensitive issues in international security, arms control and disarmament. David Hamburg served on CISAC board during his tenure as the Carnegie Corporation president, and facilitated numerous “linkages” between CISAC and the Corporation’s efforts in avoiding nuclear war and preventing deadly conflict. The subseries has an overlap with Subseries I.7 (PDC) and I.8 (Eastern Bloc), particularly IOM/NAS/NRC/CISAC materials from 80s contain substantial amount of material relating to the USSR. NOTE: Be careful not to confuse Committee on International Security and Arms Control with Stanford's "CISAC" (Center for International Security and Arms Control, whose name was later changed to Center for International Security and Cooperation).
    - Subject files, 1982- (Box 650)
    - Subject files, 1982-1984 (Box 651)
    - Subject files, 1984-1986 (Box 652)
    - Subject files, 1985-1987 (Box 653)
    - Subject files, 1985-1987 (Box 654)
    - Background Materials, 1980-1987 (Box 655)
- Series II: United States Government
  The series pertains to Hamburg’s advisory work for various agencies from the executive branch of the U.S. Government. It contains correspondence with various government officials and the White House, minutes of meetings, research materials, recommendations and reports. The series initially contained a large number of printed official U.S. government documents, which are preserved and available elsewhere. These publications were discarded, unless they contained manuscript notes by Hamburg; only their title or front pages were retained in order to document the fact of their presence in the collection.
  - Subseries II.1: President's Committee of Advisors on Science and Technology (PCAST)
    David Hamburg served on President's Committee of Advisors on Science and Technology Policy (PCAST) within the Office of Science and Technology Policy, a part of the Executive Office of the President (EOP) of U.S. Government. The subseries contains materials on PCAST initiative on race, biodiversity initiative, Education Panel and Children's Initiative, memoranda to President Clinton, and reports to Vice-President Al Core, materials related to the National Science and Technology Council. OSTP files contain a substantial amount of CCSTG materials and reports; for additional CCSTG documents see the Carnegie Corporation of New York Series IV.B
    - PCAST subject files, January 1995-October 1995 (Box 206, Folder 1-30)
    - PCAST subject files, October 1995-June 1996 (Box 207, Folder 1-39)
    - PCAST subject files, July 1996-February 1997 (Box 208, Folder 1-32)
    - PCAST subject files, March 1997-June 1997 (Box 209, Folder 1-40)
    - PCAST subject files, July 1997-October 1997 (Box 210, Folder 1-36)
    - PCAST subject files, November 1997-May 1998 (Box 211, Folder 1-22)
    - PCAST subject files, June 1998-February 1999 (Box 212, Folder 1-26)
    - PCAST subject files, February 1999-September 1999 (Box 213, Folder 1-32)
    - PCAST subject files, September 1999-April 2000 (Box 214, Folder 1-33)
    - PCAST subject files, May 2000-2001, undated (Box 215, Folder 1-31)
    - PCAST subject files, 1994-2000 (Box 216, Folder 1-30)
  - Subseries II.2: Presidential Advisory Committee on Gulf War Veterans' Illnesses
    Materials relating to Hamburg’s participation in Presidential Advisory Committee on Gulf War Veterans Illnesses, also within the Office of Science and Technology Policy, and part of the National Science and Technology Council. It includes background materials on stress and immunity from 1985-1996, and documents related to the CCSTG, PDC, and Children and Youth programs of Carnegie Corporation. The files are arranged chronologically.
    - PCAST subject files, 1995-May 1996 (Box 217, Folder 1-50)
    - Gulf War Illnesses Materials, May 1996-September 1996 (Box 218, Folder 1-35)
    - Gulf War Illnesses Materials, September 1996-May 1997 (Box 219, Folder 1-20)
    - Gulf War Illnesses Materials, June 1997-1998 (Box 220, Folder 1-22)
    - Gulf War Illnesses Materials, November 1992-December 1992 (Box 221, Folder 1-21)
  - Subseries II.3: Office of President Clinton
    The subseries documents David Hamburg’s participation in Bill Clinton’s Transition Office in November 1992 through April 1993. It also contains materials relating to Hamburgs White House meetings of 1997-1999.
    - Clinton Transition Office, December 1992-April 1993 (Box 714, Folder 1-15)
    - Clinton Transition Office - end, 1997-1999 (Box 715, Folder 1-8)
    - White House Meetings, 1990-1994 (Box 715, Folder 9-16)
  - Subseries II.4: Secretary of Energy Advisory Board
    The series contains the correspondence from the period of Hamburg’s service on the Department of Energy Secretary of Energy Advisory Board (SEAB).
    - Secretary of Energy Advisory Board Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 716)
    - Meeting files, 1984-1987 (Box 717)
  - Subseries II.5: Chief of Naval Operations Executive Panel
    Hamburg served on a number of policy advisory boards in the international security field, including the Executive Panel for the Chief of Naval Operations. He was also a member of the Defense Policy Board of the Department of Defense under U. S. Secretary of Defense William J. Perry. The series contains correspondence, minutes of meetings, travel reports, printed matter.
    - Subject Files and Printed materials, 1984-1997 (Box 718)
    - Subject Files and Printed materials (Box 719)
- Series III: Correspondence
  Alphabetical correspondence files under individual or institutional names were maintained in many offices throughout Dr. Hamburg’s career. This is the record of Dr. Hamburg’s external correspondence in his various capacities. During his subsequent projects, he often took some of the files out of their original sequences, as he needed them, and added them to new filing systems, associated with his ongoing work. Restoring original order proved impossible, and all these correspondence files have been sorted into a single alphabetical sequence for Individuals (III.1) and another one for Institutions (III.2). From the later period, we have chronological correspondence as well (Series III.3).
  - Subseries III.1: Individuals
    Series contain a mix of personal and professional correspondence with numerous scientists and educators, public figures, leaders of organized philanthropy, government officials, board members and staff of various national, foreign and international organizations, who corresponded with David Hamburg throughout his career. Many of the letters also include attachments, such as typescripts of works sent to Hamburg for his review, and other supplementary material. As indicated by folder titles, some files in the sequence contain small amounts of correspondence with several individuals, whose names are in the same alphabetical range.
    - Aa-Ai (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Abeel, Maud, 1999- (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - Abelson, Philip H., 1982-1998 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Abram, Morris, 1982- (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Abramowitz, Morton I, 1991-1996 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Abrams, Herbert L., 1980-1996 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Abshire, David, 1991-1996 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Adams, John H., 1995- (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Adams, Robert M., 1984- (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Adams, Ruth, 1985-1992 (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - Adler, Nancy, 1998-2000 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - Adubifa, O. Akinyinka, 1994-1999 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Ak-Ax (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Akil, Huda, 1997- (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - Akinkugbe, Oladipo, 1985-1988 (Box 228, Folder 14)
    - Akselrad, Sidney, 1978-1996 (Box 228, Folder 15)
    - Alberts, Bruce, 1993-1998 (Box 228, Folder 16)
    - Albright, Madeline, 1997-1998 (Box 228, Folder 17)
    - Alexander, Byron, 1976-1979 (Box 228, Folder 18)
    - Alexander, Lamar, 1988-1992 (Box 228, Folder 19)
    - Allen, Beverley, 1999- (Box 228, Folder 20)
    - Alleyne, George, 1992-1999 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Allison, Graham, 1980-1999 (Box 229, Folder 2-6)
    - Allison, Graham, 1982-2001 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Allyn, Bruce, 1991-1994 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Am-An (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Ames, Oakes, 1992-1993 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Amu, Ngozi, 2000- (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Angeby, Ragnar, 2002- (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Angel, Ada, 1977-1998 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Angel, David, 1980-1989 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Angelson, Meredith, 1998- (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Angle, Martha, 1977-1992 (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - Anlyan, William G., 1994- (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Annan, Ekua, 1998- (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - Annan, Kofi, 1996-2001 (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - Anthony, Virginia Q., 1993-1994 (Box 230, Folder 13)
    - Ap-Az (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - Arbatov, Alexi, 1990-1995 (Box 230, Folder 14)
    - Arbatov, Georgi, 1979-1991 (Box 230, Folder 15)
    - Arciniega, Tomas, 1982-1992 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Aronow, Lewis, 1981-1987 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Arons, Barbara, 1983- (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Aronson, Michael, 2000- (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Arrow, Kenneth J, 1982- (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Arsenian, Deana, 1983-1999 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Aspden, Jeanette, 1999-2000 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Aspin, Les (Secretary of Defense), 1992-1993 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Astor, Brooke, 1984-1998 (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - Atkinson, Rita, 1979-1984 (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - August, Diane, 1984- (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - Ausubel, Jesse, 1990-2000 (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - Ausubel, Jesse, 1994-1996 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Avery, Mary Ellen, 1982-1993 (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Axworthy, Lloyd, 1999- (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Babbitt, Bruce, 1985-1992 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - Bac-Bar (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Bader, William, 1993-1994 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Badsha, Omar, 1985-1989 (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - Baird, Zoe, 1994-2000 (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - Baker, Howard J. Jr., 1983-1991 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - Baker, William O., 1986-1999 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - Ball, Robert, 1979-1996 (Box 259, Folder 9-10)
    - Ball, Robert, 1991-1994 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Ballentine, Karen, 1994-2000 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Baltes, Paul, 1995-1999 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Baltimore, David, 1989-1991 (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Bandura, Albert, 1984-1998 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Bane. Mary-Jo, 1987-1991 (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Banks, James, 1983-1993 (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Banta, David, 1980-1982 (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Bar-Bax (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Barchas, Jack, 1975-2001 (Box 260, Folder 9-10)
    - Barchas, Jack, 1997-2000 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Barchas, Patricia, 1975-1981 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Barnes, Harry, 1995-2000 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Barondess, Jeremiah A., 1978-2001 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Barraclough, Solon, 1983-1983 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Bateson, Patrick, 1989-1995 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Bauer, Harold, 1971-1994 (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - Baugh, Jim, 1975-1981 (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Bazelon, David L., 1977-1992 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Bea-Bel (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Bearn, Alexander, 1982-1996 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Beattie, Dick, 1990-2000 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Beaumont, Kathryn S., 1973-1976 (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Beauregard, Rebecca ("Becky"), 1985- (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Beck, Aaron, ND- (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Becker, Gerald, 1985-1994 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Bel-Berm (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Bell, David, 1983- (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Bell, Karen, 1994-1996 (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Bell, Peter D., 1980-2001 (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - Bendow, Zerfinesh, 1982- (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - Bennet, Douglas J., 1985-1996 (Box 233, Folder 11)
    - Berger, Louis, 1975-1981 (Box 233, Folder 12)
    - Berger, Philip, 1974-1987 (Box 233, Folder 13)
    - Bergman-Riss, Emilie, 1976-1993 (Box 233, Folder 14)
    - Bergstrom, Sune, 1976-2000 (Box 233, Folder 15)
    - Berman, Leo, 1979- (Box 233, Folder 16)
    - Berman, Morton, 1980- (Box 233, Folder 17)
    - Bernard, Lewis, 1993-1994 (Box 233, Folder 18)
    - Bern-Bey (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Bernstein, Robert L., 1988-2000 (Box 233, Folder 19)
    - Berresford, Susan, 1988-1996 (Box 233, Folder 20)
    - Beschel, Robert Jr. "Bob", 1988-1994 (Box 234, Folder 1-4)
    - Bevan, William, 1980-1996 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Bezanson, Keith, 1992-1996 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Bha-Blay (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Bienenstock, Arthur, 1998-1999 (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Billington, James, 1996-1998 (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Bing, Peter, 1975-1997 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Bingaman, Jeff, 1985-1997 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Bisbee, Gary, 1982- (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Blackwill, Robert, 1991-1998 (Box 239, Folder 6-8)
    - Ble-Blu (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Blendon, Robert, 1982-1992 (Box 239, Folder 9)
    - Blight, James, 1986-1994 (Box 240, Folder 1-2)
    - Blobel, Gunter, 1999-1999 (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Bloom, Barry, 1998-2000 (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Bloom. Floyd, 1974-1999 (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Blumenthal, David, 1982-1992 (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Blumenthal, Martin, 1993-1995 (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - Blumenthal, Monica, 1973-1980 (Box 240, Folder 8)
    - Bo- (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Boesak, Allen, 1985-1990 (Box 240, Folder 9)
    - Bohen, Fred, 1999- (Box 240, Folder 10)
    - Boitano, Caroline, 1977-1999 (Box 240, Folder 12)
    - Bok, Derek, 1978-1994 (Box 240, Folder 11)
    - Bond, Douglas, 1974-1977 (Box 240, Folder 13)
    - Botvin, Gilbert, 1993-1996 (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Boufford, Jo Ivey, 2000-2000 (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Bourne, Peter, 1976-1999 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Boutros-Ghali, Boutros, 1991-1999 (Box 241, Folder 4-9)
    - Bowen, William G, 1988-2000 (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - Bowlby, John, 1960-1995 (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Boyer, Ernest, 1982-1995 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Bra-Bri (Box 247, Folder 3-4)
    - Brademas, John, 1983-2001 (Box 242, Folder 3-7)
    - Bradley, Bill, 1993-1996 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Brandt, Edward N. Jr, 1982-1995 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Branscombe, Lewis M., 1980-1998 (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Brasher, James, 1990-1996 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Braunwald, Eugene, 1982-1983 (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Brenner, Theo, 1995-1998 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Brest, Paul, 1999-2000 (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Bro (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Bro-Bu (Box 248, Folder 1-2)
    - Brodie, Kevin, 1975-2000 (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Brody, Eugene, 1973-1997 (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Brokaw, Tom, 1986-1996 (Box 243, Folder 10)
    - Bromley, D. Allen, 1989-1994 (Box 243, Folder 11)
    - Bronte, Lydia, 1983-1997 (Box 243, Folder 12)
    - Brooks, Harvey, 1985-1985 (Box 243, Folder 13)
    - Brooks-Gunn, Jeanne, 1984-1994 (Box 243, Folder 14)
    - Brown, Bertram, 1986-1990 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Dyke, 1980-1981 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Brown, Gloria Primm, 1980-1997 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Harold, 1977-1998 (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Sarah, 1976-2001 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - Brown, Scott, 1992-1997 (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - Brundtland, Gro Harlem, 1989-2001 (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - Bryant, John, 1978-2000 (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - Bryant, Thomas, 1977-1988 (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - Buffet, Warren, 1984-1992 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Bulger, Roger, 1976-1995 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Bundy, Mcgeorge, 1983-1997 (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Bunker, John P., 1977-1986 (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Bunney, Benjamin, 1994-1996 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - Bunney, William Jr., 1979-1999 (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - Burger, Ed, 2000-2000 (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - Burke, Sheila, 1984-1996 (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Burnell, E. Langdon, 1978-1980 (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - Burton, John W., ND- (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - Bush, Donald, 1981-1982 (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - Bushey, Bruce, 1983-1985 (Box 245, Folder 11)
    - Busse, Curt, 1974-1975 (Box 245, Folder 12)
    - Butler, John, 1981-1981 (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - Butler, Owen Bradford, 1981-1998 (Box 245, Folder 15-16)
    - Butler, Robert N., 1977-1993 (Box 245, Folder 17)
    - Butler,.Lewis H., 1982-1989 (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - Butts, Roger, 1998-1998 (Box 245, Folder 19)
    - Bwakira, Cyrilla, 2000-2000 (Box 245, Folder 20)
    - Cab-Car (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Califano, Joseph, 1977-2001 (Box 249, Folder 1-5)
    - Campbell, Colin, 1992-1999 (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - Campbell, Kurt, 1984-1999 (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Canfield, Robert, 1982-1982 (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - Caper, Philip, 1984-1984 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Car-Cha (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Carey, William D., 1987-1998 (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - Carnegie, Andrew, 1989-1996 (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Carnesale, Albert, 1985-1998 (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - Carstairs, Morris, 1965-1981 (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - Carter, Ashton, 1992-2001 (Box 250, Folder 8)
    - Carter, Beverley, 1975-1982 (Box 250, Folder 9)
    - Carter, Carlyn Brown, 1977-1979 (Box 250, Folder 10)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1992-1999 (Box 250, Folder 11-12)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1977-1995 (Box 251, Folder 1-5)
    - Casper, Gerhard and Regina, 1992-1996 (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Celeste, Richard, 1991-1999 (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Cha-Coh (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Chafee, John H., 1992-1996 (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Chalmers, Thomas, 1978-1996 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Champion, Hale, 1979-1999 (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - Chancellor, John, 1993-1999 (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Charles, Bernard, 1984-1991 (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - Chase, Robert, 1977-1998 (Box 252, Folder 8)
    - Chayes, Abram J, 1983-1995 (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - Chelalal, Cesar, 1992-1995 (Box 252, Folder 10)
    - Cheney, Richard, 1988-1989 (Box 252, Folder 11)
    - Chiles, Lawton, 1988-1998 (Box 252, Folder 12)
    - Chiles, Lawton, 1989-1998 (Box 253, Folder 1-2)
    - Choppin, Purnell, 1985-1994 (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Christmas, June Jackson, 1978-1996 (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Christopher, Warren, 1988-1998 (Box 253, Folder 5-7)
    - Christopher, Warren (Clinton's) Secretarty of State; Deputy Attorney General, 1977-2000 (Box 254, Folder 1-8)
    - Ciaranello, Roland, 1977-1995 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - Cisneros, Henry, 1984-1995 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Clark, Dick, 1983-1997 (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - Clark, Jack G, 1983-1992 (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - Clausen, John, 1976-1984 (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - Clinton, Bill, 1993-2001 (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Clinton, Bill, 1988-2002 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, 1972-2000 (Box 256, Folder 2-5)
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, 1996-1997 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Coelho, George and Rani, 1973-1998 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Coh-Cor (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Cohen, Alex, 1998-2000 (Box 257)
    - Cohen, Donald, 1992-1998 (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Francis, 1976-1981 (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Cohen, Jack, 1975-1975 (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Cohen, Lois Ruth Kushner, 1981-1993 (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - Cohen, Michael I, 1990-1998 (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Cohen, Stuart J, 1983-1987 (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Cohn, Victor, 1990-1990 (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Cole, Michael, 1987-1995 (Box 257, Folder 10)